Finding Aid for Michigan Historical Records Survey records, 1936-1942
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Transcripts of County Records
  - Gratiot County
    - Proceedings of the Board of Supervisors
      - Liber 6 October 1885-January 1890 (Reel 63)
      - Liber 7 October 1897-October 1900 (Reel 63)
  - Houghton County
    - Proceedings of the Board of Supervisors
      - Vol. 1 August 1846-August 1861 (Reel 63)
  - Ingham County
    - Abstract of Supervisors' Proceedings
      - October 1838-October 1865 (Reel 63)
    - Proceedings of the Board of Supervisors
      - Vol. 1 October 1838-April 1847 (Reel 63)
      - Salaries 1939-1940 (Reel 63)
      - 1940-1941 (Reel 63)
  - Ionia County
    - Abstract of Supervisors' Proceedings
      - June 1846-April 1853 (Reel 64)
      - October 1905-January 1913 (Reel 64)
    - Proceedings of the Board of Supervisors
      - April 1837-October 1857 (Reel 64)
    - Miscellaneous Accounts
      - 1838-1842 (Reel 64)
  - Isabella County 1859-1863 (Box 11)
  - Jackson County 1837-1885 (Box 11)
  - Jackson County 1837-1885 (Box 12)
  - Kalamazoo County
    - Abstract of Supervisors' Proceedings
      - October 1834-October 1899 (Reel 64)
    - Proceedings of the Board of Supervisors
      - October 1834-October 1857 (Reel 64)
  - Kalkaska County 1861-1941 (Box 12)
  - Kent County 1845-1888 (Box 13)
  - Kent County 1845-1888 (Box 14)
  - Keweenaw County 1861-1883 (Box 14)
  - Lake County 1869-1921 (Box 14)
  - Leelanau County 1863-1919 (Box 15)
  - Lenawee County
    - Abstract of Supervisors' Proceedings
      - April 1852-March 1938 (Reel 64)
    - Proceedings of the Board of Supervisors
      - April 1852-October 1855 (Reel 64)
      - April 1852-April 1916 (Reel 64)
      - April 1852-April 1916 (cont.) (Reel 65)
    - First Canvass
      - November 1852 (Reel 65)
  - Luce County 1936 (Box 15)
  - Mackinac County 1859-1884 (Box 15)
  - Macomb County
    - Proceedings of the Board of Supervisors
      - July 1827-October 1838 (Reel 65)
      - October 1856-February 1860 (Reel 65)
  - Manistee County 1855-1876 (Box 15)
  - Marquette County 1852-1883 (Box 15)
  - Mason County 1855-1909 (Box 16)
  - Mecosta County 1859-1900 (Box 16)
  - Menominee County 1863-1881 (Box 17)
  - Midland County 1855-1875 (Box 17)
  - Missaukee County 1871-1938 (Box 17)
  - Montcalm County 1850-1939 (Box 17)
  - Montmorency County
    - Proceedings of the Board of Supervisors
      - June 1881-October 1887 (Reel 65)
      - January 1887-May 1887 (Reel 65)
  - Newaygo County 1852-1893 (Box 17)
  - Oakland County
    - Abstract of Supervisors' Proceedings
      - April 1828-October 1852 (Reel 65)
    - Proceedings of the Board of Supervisors
      - July 1827-March 1837 (Reel 65)
      - July 1827-October 1849 (Reel 65)
  - Oceana County 1855-1925 (Box 17)
  - Ogemaw County
    - Proceedings of the Board of Supervisors (Reel 66)
      - Vol. 1 April 1876-March 1879, circa October 1876-January 1882, April 1880-October 1882, April 1879-January 1885 (Reel 66)
      - Vol. 2 June 1885-January 1892, October 1897 (Reel 66)
  - Ontonagon County 1853-1864, 1881-1924, 1938 (Box 18)
  - Osceola County 1869-1941 (Box 18)
  - Oscoda County 1881-1907 (Box 18)
  - Otsego County 1875-1941 (Box 19)
  - Ottawa County 1838-1854, 1937-1939 (Box 20)
  - Presque Isle County 1871-1881 (Box 20)
  - Roscommon County 1875-1940 (Box 20)
  - Saginaw County
    - Proceedings of the Board of Supervisors
      - Vol. A October 1835-November 1842 (Reel 67)
      - Vol. B August 1858-July 1866 (Reel 67)
  - St. Clair County
    - Proceedings of the Board of Supervisors
      - Vol. 1 March 1833-May 1839 (Reel 67)
  - Sanilac County
    - Abstract of Supervisors' Proceedings
      - October 1850-December 1926 (Reel 67)
  - Schoolcraft County 1871-1890 (Box 20)
  - Shiawassee County 1838-1860 (Box 20)
  - Tuscola County
    - Abstract of Supervisors' Proceedings
      - January 1851-January 1933 (Reel 67)
    - Proceedings of the Board of Supervisors
      - Vol. 1 November 1850-November 1860 (Reel 67)
      - Vol. 2 June 1856-October 1859 (Reel 67)
  - Washtenaw County
    - 1835 (Box 20)
    - 1867-1872 (Box 20)
    - 1901 (Box 20)
    - Assessment Rolls
      - 1865-1937 (Box 20)
  - Wexford County (Box 20)
  - 1869-1892
    - 1939 (Box 20)
- Transcripts of Municipal Records
  (These transcripts have been microfilmed; a complete listing of all the transcripts, both on microfilm and hard copy, follows the listing of the contents of roll 68.)
  - Alpena 1871-1874 (Box 21)
  - Battle Creek 1859-1865, 1940 (Box 21)
  - Bay City
    - Council Proceedings
      - Vol. A April 1878 (Reel 68)
  - Cheboygan
    - City Charter (Box 21)
    - Ordinances
      - 1871 (Box 21)
      - 1882 (Box 21)
      - 1888 (Box 21)
      - 1891 (Box 21)
      - 1917 (Box 21)
  - Detroit 1894-1934 (Box 22)
  - Escanaba
    - Council Proceedings (Published in "Iron Port")
      - April 1883-February 1889 (Reel 68)
    - Council Proceedings
      - April 1889 (Reel 68)
    - Abstract of Proceedings
      - July 1901-February 1905 (Reel 68)
    - Ordinances 1-22 (missing 16 and 20) (Reel 68)
  - Grand Rapids 1838-1873 (Box 22)
  - Grand Rapids 1838-1873 (Box 23)
  - Grand Rapids 1838-1873 (Box 24)
  - Hamtramck
    - 1901-1910 (Box 24)
    - 1911-1915 (Box 25)
    - 1915-1918 (Box 26)
    - 1919-1921 (Box 27)
    - 1921-1923 (Box 28)
    - 1923 (Box 29)
    - 1923-1924 (Box 30)
    - 1924-1925 (Box 31)
    - 1925-1926 (Box 32)
    - 1926-1927 (Box 33)
    - 1927-1928 (Box 34)
    - 1929-1930 (Box 35)
    - 1930-1931 (Box 36)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 37)
    - 1932-1933 (Box 38)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 39)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 40)
    - 1935-1936 (Box 41)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 42)
    - 1937-1938 (Box 43)
  - Jackson
    - 1857-1858 (Box 44)
    - Ordinances 1857 (Box 44)
  - Marquette (Box 44)
    - 1868-1874 (Box 44)
    - Laws of Michigan relating to Marquette 1859-1907 (Box 44)
  - Menominee 1883-1885 (Box 44)
  - Muskegon 1861-1862 (Box 44)
  - Negaunee
    - 1866-1873 (Box 44)
    - Negaunee Township 1858-1873 (Box 44)
  - Niles
    - Miscellaneous Records
      - May 1838-April 1865 (Reel 68)
    - Standing Rules for Common Council 1-27
  - Port Huron
    - 1849-1850 (Box 44)
    - 1891 (Box 44)
    - Ordinances 1849-1941 (Box 44)
- Maps
  The series Maps, consists of maps of the counties drawn by H.R.S. workers on letter-size paper in preparation for publication in the guide for each county. Oftentimes there is a map of Michigan with the given county highlighted to show its location, followed by several maps of that county in varying levels of detail, drawn with some care, frequently in color. The best representative sample of each has been retained, with all duplicates discarded. After filming, these maps have been preserved and grouped together, arranged alphabetically by county. In addition, there are a few maps, too large to microfilm or not really related to the H.R.S., which have been removed to the Bentley Library's map collection.
  - Maps (Box 45)
- Architectural drawings
  Architectural Drawings consist of floor plans and/or elevations of city and county buildings. The drawings are arranged alphabetically by county. On the whole the drawings were not microfilmed, although drawings from some of the HCA files, which were filmed, have been added to this series.)
  - Alcona
    - Alcona County Courthouse (Box 46)
  - Alpena
    - Alpena County Courthouse (Box 46)
    - Alpena City Hall (Box 46)
  - Arenac
    - Arenac County Courthouse (Box 46)
  - Baraga
    - Baraga County Courthouse (Box 46)
  - Bay
    - Bay County Building (Box 46)
  - Benzie
    - Benzie County Courthouse (Box 46)
  - Berrien
    - St. Joseph City Hall (Box 46)
  - Calhoun
    - Calhoun County Courthouse (Box 46)
  - Cheboygan
    - Cheboygan County Courthouse (Box 46)
    - County Jail (Box 46)
    - Mackinaw City Hall (Box 46)
    - Cheboygan City Hall (Box 46)
  - Chippewa
    - Chippewa County Courthouse (Box 46)
  - Crawford
    - Crawford County Courthouse (Box 46)
    - Crawford County Jail (Box 46)
  - Delta
    - Delta County Road Commission (Box 46)
    - Escanaba City Hall (Box 46)
  - Dickinson
    - Dickinson County Courthouse (Box 46)
    - Social Welfare Bureau in County Health Building (Box 46)
    - County Jail (Box 46)
  - Eaton
    - Eaton County Courthouse (Box 46)
  - Emmet
    - Emmet County Courthouse (Box 46)
  - Gogebic
    - Gogebic County Courthouse (Box 46)
  - Grand Traverse
    - Grand Traverse County Courthouse (Box 46)
    - County Jail (Box 46)
    - County Clerk's Vault (Box 46)
    - Leach Building (Box 46)
  - Huron
    - Bad Axe Courthouse (Box 46)
  - Ionia
    - Ionia County Courthouse (Box 46)
  - Iosco
    - Iosco County Courthouse (Box 46)
    - County Jail (Box 46)
    - Iron (Box 46)
    - Iron County Courthouse (Box 46)
    - Plat of courthouse block (Box 46)
    - H.C.A. files (Box 46)
  - Isabella
    - Isabella County Courthouse (Box 46)
  - Kalamazoo
    - Kalamazoo County Courthouse (Box 46)
  - Kalkaska
    - Kalkaska County Courthouse (Box 46)
  - Kent
    - Kent County Courthouse (Box 46)
  - Keweenaw
    - Keweenaw County Courthouse (Box 46)
  - Leelanau
    - Leelanau County Courthouse (Box 46)
  - Livingston
    - Livingston County Courthouse (Box 46)
  - Luce
    - Luce County Courthouse (Box 46)
  - Mackinac
    - Mackinac County Courthouse (Box 46)
  - Marquette
    - Marquette County Courthouse (Box 46)
    - Marquette City Hall (Box 46)
    - Ishpeming City Hall (Box 46)
    - Negaunee City Hall (Box 46)
  - Mason
    - Mason County Courthouse (Box 46)
  - Menominee
    - Menominee County Courthouse (Box 46)
    - County Road Commission (Box 46)
  - Midland
    - Midland County Courthouse (Box 46)
  - Missaukee
    - Missaukee County Courthouse (Box 46)
  - Monroe
    - Monroe County Courthouse (Box 46)
  - Montmorency
    - Montmorency County Courthouse (Box 46)
  - Muskegon
    - Muskegon County Courthouse (Box 46)
    - Administration Building for Muskegon County (Box 46)
  - Osceola
    - Osceola County Courthouse (Box 46)
  - Oscoda
    - Oscoda County Courthouse (Box 46)
  - Otsego
    - Otsego County Courthouse (Box 46)
  - Ottawa
    - Ottawa County Courthouse (Box 46)
  - Presque Isle
    - Presque Isle County Courthouse (Box 46)
  - Saginaw
    - Saginaw County Courthouse (Box 46)
  - St. Clair
    - City Hall and Courthouse, Port Huron (Box 46)
    - Seal of the City of Port Huron (Box 46)
  - St. Joseph
    - St. Joseph County Courthouse (Box 46)
  - Sanilac
    - Sanilac County Building (Box 46)
  - Schoolcraft
    - Schoolcraft County Jail (Box 46)
  - Van Buren
    - Van Buren County Courthouse (Box 46)
  - Washtenaw
    - Washtenaw County Road Commission (Box 46)
  - Wayne
    - Wayne County Building (Box 46)
    - Detroit City Hall (Box 46)
    - Municipal Garage (Box 46)
    - Department of Water Supply (Box 46)
    - Detroit Institute of Arts (Box 46)
    - Hamtramck Municipal Building (Box 46)
    - Seal of the City of Hamtramck (Box 46)
    - Hamtramck Welfare Department Day Nursery (Box 46)
    - Hamtramck Justice Courts (Box 46)
    - Hamtramck City Attorney (Box 46)
    - Hamtramck City Engineer's Building (Box 46)
    - Hamtramck Board of Health (Box 46)
    - Hamtramck Library (Box 46)
    - Hamtramck Recreation Center (Box 46)
    - Hamtramck City Physician (Box 46)
    - Hamtramck Welfare Unemployment Office (Box 46)
- Photographs
  The small Photographs series is primarily images of government buildings (courthouses, city halls, jails etc.) with a few images of local events or activities. The photos are arranged by county. The photographs were not microfilmed
  - Crawford
    - Crawford County Courthouse, Grayling (Box 46)
  - Eaton
    - Christian Missionary Alliance, Central Church (Box 46)
  - Emmet
    - Emmet County Courthouse (Box 46)
    - Jackson County Courthouses (Box 46)
  - Kalamazoo
    - Kalamazoo County Courthouse (Box 46)
  - Keweenaw
    - Keweenaw County Courthouse, Eagle River (Box 46)
  - Marquette
    - City Hall, Marquette (Box 46)
    - Peter White Public Library, Marquette (Box 46)
    - Forsyth Township Hall, Gwinn (Box 46)
    - West Branch Township Halls (Box 46)
    - Turin Township Hall (Box 46)
  - Midland
    - Midland County Courthouse (Box 46)
  - Muskegon
    - Site of first county offices, Muskegon (Box 46)
    - Muskegon County Courthouses, Muskegon (Box 46)
  - Ogemaw
    - Ogemaw County Courthouse and Jail, West Branch (Box 46)
  - Osceola
    - Osceola County Courthouse, Hersey (when that was the county seat) (Box 46)
    - First school in county, Evart (Box 46)
  - Ottawa
    - Ottawa County Courthouses (Box 46)
  - Saginaw
    - Saginaw County Courthouse (Box 46)
    - 1849 site of present city hall, Saginaw (present as of ca. 1940) (Box 46)
    - The old "Academy", first schoolhouse in East Saginaw (Box 46)
    - Lumberjacks at work (Box 46)
  - Tuscola
    - Tuscola County Courthouses (Box 46)
  - Wayne
    - Wayne County Building, Detroit (Box 46)
  - Wexford
    - Viking Water Festival floats, Cadillac (Box 46)
- Historical Records Survey Correspondence
  The Historical Records Survey Correspondence series consists of correspondence between field workers in the counties and their supervisors in district offices or the state H.R.S. office contains descriptive and historical information about the counties as well as information concerning the workings of the H.R.S. project. In some areas the work went along quite smoothly, but in others the field workers faced numerous difficulties: getting permission to examine government records and to have a place to work, facing officials whose attitude ranged from indifference to outright hostility; attempting to inventory records which were poorly organized and stored in inaccessible places; and even obtaining adequate training and basic office supplies from the W.P.A. Charles Johnson, a field worker in Ionia County, wrote articulately on the workings of the project and his letters make good reading (see Roll 13). Three counties - Alger, Ingham, and Marquette - had H.R.S. district supervisors' offices, so their correspondence files contain information about whole regions as well as good descriptions of the project (letters which mentioned only one county have been transferred to that county's files). H.R.S. correspondence is also a source of information about county records. Sometimes it reveals what had happened to records which no longer existed when the survey was conducted and sometimes it is a source of inventory information - in the case of Ingham County the only source, since both the forms and the completed inventory (if there ever was one) are lost. Within each county, correspondence is arranged chronologically and anything of a routine or insignificant nature has been discarded. General instructions, issued to each field worker in the state, have not been retained for each county but only where they were first found in processing and so would tend to be concentrated at the beginning of the alphabetical listing of counties. Any researcher studying the H.R.S. project would want to consult all of the correspondence; therefore, in addition to each county's correspondence being microfilmed with its other material, all the correspondence has been preserved after filming and grouped together, arranged alphabetically by county.
  - County (Box 47)
  - Municipals (Box 47)
- Survey forms of 1987 Survey of Records in Counties and Municipalities
  (arranged in two alphabetical sequences, by county and then by municipality). The survey revealed the dates and condition of the records held by the respective governments, any transfer or microfilming of records, and quality of storage facilities.)
  - County Surveys (Box 47)
  - Municipal Surveys (Box 47)
1987 Survey of Records of Records in Counties and Municipalities
In 1987 the Bentley Library conducted a survey of the counties and municipalities whose transcripts of government records were included in the H.R.S. collection. It revealed that most of the originals still exist in their home locales, but some have been lost, burned, or discarded, leaving the library with probably the only extant copies of those records. Although the bulk of the transcripts (55 linear feet of material in 44 Paige boxes) will remain as they are, the unique ones (10 linear feet) have been microfilmed. Most of the counties of Michigan are represented, as well as fifteen municipalities (see contents list). All are valuable sources of historical information.
COUNTY RECORDS
Alcona, 1876-
Allegan, 1926-
Alpena, 1871-
Antrim, 1863-
Arenac, 1883-
Bay, 1874-1883, 1887-1908, 1938-
Benzie, 1869-
Berrien, 1832-
Calhoun, all
Cass, 1933- (State Archives, 1831-1868, 1880-1955, available on microfilm)
Cheboygan, 1855-
Chippewa, all
Clare, 1871-
Crawford, 1895-
Delta, all
Dickinson, all
Eaton, 1838-
Emmet, 1859-1873, 1885-1922, 1925-
Genesee, 1948- (published, 1901-) (State Archives, 1835-1972, available on microfilm)
Gladwin, 1875-
Gogebic, 1887-
Grand Traverse, 1853-
Gratiot, 1856- (except Libers 5 & 6)
Houghton, mid 1880's-
Ingham, 1888- (State Archives, 1838-1931, available on microfilm)
Ionia, 1838-
Isabella, 1859-
Jackson, 1833-
Kalamazoo, 1842- (State Archives, 1864-1869, 1897-1948)
Kalkaska, late 1800's-
Kent, 1845-
Keweenaw, 1861-
Lake, 1871-
Leelanau, 1863-
Lenawee, 1929-
Mackinac, 1859-
Macomb, 1909-
Manistee, 1855-
Marquette, 1852-
Mason, 1855-
Mecosta, 1859-
Menominee, 1863-
Midland, 1959- (State Archives, 1855-1958, available on microfilm)
Missaukee, 1871-
Montcalm, 1850-
Montmorency, 1963-
Muskegon, ? (State Archives, 1859-1936, available on microfilm)
Oakland, 1942-
Oceana, 1855-
Ogemaw, 1885-
Ontonagon, 1853-1863, 1881-
Osceola, 1869-
Oscoda, 1881-
Otsego, 1875-
Ottawa, 1838-
Presque Isle, 1871-
Roscommon, 1875-
Saginaw, 1845?-
St. Clair, 1961- (State Archives, 1833-1961, available on microfilm)
Sanilac, 1885-
Schoolcraft, 1871-
Shiawassee, 1838-
Tuscola, 1851-
Washtenaw, 1835-
Wayne, ? (State Archives, 1869-1872, 1879-1944, 1946-1947)
Wexford, 1869-
Municipal Records
Alpena, 1871-
Battle Creek, 1850, 1859-
Bay City, 1897-
Escanaba, 1889-
Grand Rapids, 1838-
Hamtramck, 1901-1909, 1914-
Jackson, 1856-
Marquette, 1868-
Menominee, 1883-
Muskegon, 1861-
Negaunee, 1858-
Niles, 1867-
State Library of Michigan
(From the Library of Michigan publication "Genealogy Update" November, 1988)
General
Calendar of the Baptist collection of Kalamazoo College, Kalamazoo, Michigan, 1940.
Mich. Oversize CD3301 M5 No. 2
Calendar of the John C. Dancy correspondence, 1898-1910. 1941.
Mich. CD3301 M5 No. 3
Cemetery records, Jackson County, Michigan. 1936
Mich. F572.J2 C45, 1936
Directory of churches and religious organizations: Greater Detroit. 1941
Mich. BR360 D4 M5 1941
Early land transfers, Detroit and Wayne County, Michigan. 1936-1940
Mich. F372.W4 E37 1936
Early land transfers, Ingham County, Michigan, 1835-1953. 1947-1962
Mich. F572.13 E13 1947
Guide to manuscript collections in Michigan, Vol. I -Detroit. 194 1
Mich. CD 3301 M5 No. 4
Guide to manuscripts depositories In the United States, Michigan. 1940.
Mich. CD3301 M5 No. 1
Inventory of federal archives in the states, No. 21, Michigan. 1938?
Mich. CD3301 J58 (copy 1)
Jackson County directory of 1858. 1936
Mich. F572.J2 J343 1936
Land records, grantors, Kent County, Michigan. 1940
Mich. F572.K3 L35 1940
Master index to records in volumes ABC Ll, briefed from Wayne County records of Register of Deeds, volumes A to 104 (inclusive). 1940
Mich. F572.W4 E37 1936. Index
Probate records from archives of Wayne County, Michigan. 1936
Mich. F572.W4 F76 1936
Inventory of Church & Synagogue Archives
African Methodist Episcopal Church, Michigan Conference. 1940
Mich. BX8441.M3 M5 1940
Church of the Nazarene, Michigan District Assembly. 1942
Mich. BX8699.N3 M5 1942
Churches of God, Michigan Assemblies, 1941.
Mich. BX7095.C7 M5 1941
Dearborn churches. 1940.
Mich. BR560.D37 M5 1940
Evangelical and Reformed Church. 1941.
Mich. Bx7517,M5 M5 1941
Evangelical Church, Michigan Conference1941.
Mich. BX7517.M5 M5 1941
Jewish bodies. 1940.
Mich. BM223.M5 M5 1940
Pilgrim Holiness Church, Michigan District. 1942.
Mich. BX5918.P3 M5 1942
Presbyterian Church In U.S.A., Presbytery of Flint. 1941.
Mich. BX921 LF7 M5 1941
Protestant Episcopal bodies, diocese of Michigan. 1940.
Mich. BX5917.M5 M5 1940
Protestant Episcopal church, diocese of Northern Michigan. 1940.
Mich. BX3918 N93 M5 1940
Protestant Episcopal church, diocese of Western Michigan. 1940.
Mich. BX5918.W46 M5 1940
Roman Catholic church, archdiocese of Detroit. 1941.
Mich. BX 141 LM5 M5 1941
Salvation army in Michigan. 1942.
Mich. BX9716.M3 1942
Inventory of County Archives
Alger County (Munising). 194 1.
Mich. CD3307 A25 A434 1941
Alpena County (Alpena). 1942.
Mich. CD3307 A4 A46 1942
Baraga County (L'Anse). 1937.
Mich. CD3307 B 15 B37 1937
Bay County (Bay City). 1940.
Mich. CD3307 B3 B39 1940
Calhoun County (Marshall). 1941.
Mich. CD3307 C2 C34 1941
Cheboygan County (Cheboygan). 1938.
Mich. CD3307 C3 C474 1938
Delta County. 1949.
Mich. CD3307 D4 D44 1949
Genesee County (Flint). 1940.
Mich. CD3307 Q3 G43 1941
Iosco County (Tawas City). 1938
Mich. CD3307 .163 1338 1938
Iron County (Crystal Falls). 1938.
Mich. CD3307 .I66 I33 1938
Jackson County (Jackson). 1941.
Mich. CD3307 J2 J325 1941
Marquette County (Marquette). 1940
Mich. CD3307 A33 M37 1940
Muskegon County (Muskegon). 1941
Mich. CD3307 A9 M88
Vital Records
Birth records from the archives of Wayne County, Michigan. 1936.
Mich. F572 W4 B57 1936
Death records, Detroit Board of Health. 1936.
Mich. F574. D4 D439 1936
Death records, Elmwood Cemetery. 1936.
Mich. F574.D4 D4392 1936
Death records, Kent County, Michigan.1940.
Mich. F572. K3 D43 1940
Death Records, Mount Elliott Cemetery. 1937.
Mich. F372 W4 D45 1937
Kent County, Michigan, marriage records. 1936-1938.
Mich. F572 A3 K43 1936
Jackson County (Michigan) marriages 18331870: as recorded in the County Clerk's office. 1936.
Mich. 572 J2 J3252 1936
Livingston County, Michigan, marriages. 1934-1937.
Mich. F572.L8 L38 1934
Marriage records from archives of Wayne County, Michigan. 1936.
Mich. F572.W4 M37 1936
Procedures for obtaining birth records, United States and territories. 1942. Gene. C342.7 M5 1942
Vital Records from the Detroit free press. 1831-1846 - 1866-1868. 1939.
Mich. CD3307 W5 M5 1942
Burton Historical Collections, Detroit Public Library
Michigan Historical Records Survey
Reports and Correspondence
County Guides
Charlevoix, Chippewa
Clare Dickinson, Genesee, Gogebic, Houghton, Huron
Keweenaw, Lapeer, Macomb, Memominee, Midland, Oakland, St. Clair, Tuscola
Missaukee
Adventists - Assemblies of God
Christian Missionary Alliance - Baptists
Baptists (2 folders)
Church of Christ (Scientist) - Church of the Nazarene
Church of the Nazarene (Historical) -
Congregational and Christian Churches (3 folders)
Orthodox-Romanian (Eastern)
Orthodox-Russian (Eastern
Methodist Churches (4 folders)
Methodist Free Churches - Presbytery of Saginaw
United Presbyterian Churches - Roman Catholic Churches
Roman Catholic Churches
Diocese of Lansing
Diocese of Saginaw
Salvation Army
Salvation Army - Volunteers of America
Church of Jesus Christ of Latter Day Saints
Compilations of the Historical Records Survey of Michigan
Vital Statistics Holdings of Church Archives in Michigan, Wayne County
Vital Records from the Detroit Free Press
Procedures for Obtaining Birth Records, United States and Territories
Birth Records from the Archives of Wayne County, Michigan
Marriage Records from Archives of Wayne County, Michigan
Livingston County, Michigan, Marriages
Jackson County (Michigan) Marriages 1833-1870: As Recorded in the County Clerk is Office
Kent County, Michigan, Marriage Records
Death Records, Mount Elliott Cemetery
Death Records, Kent County, Michigan
Death Records, Elmwood Cemetery
Death Records, Detroit Board of Health